Dear VI Marketing and Branding:

Okie born and raised currently working at a top advertising agency in Houston, Love Advertising. However, I want to find my way back home to Oklahoma and VI Marketing and Branding is the perfect place for someone of my age and talent to expand their knowledge in the wonderful world of advertising and marketing. The passion and capabilities expressed at your agency is outstanding. We would be the perfect fit for each other, with my experience as a project manager, work ethic and media background. The available position as Marketing Coordinator is just the job for me.

Right out of college I jumped head first into gaining the necessary experience to begin the long road to success. Advertising and marketing is not only my chosen career, but also a lifestyle. In this chosen profession you must love what you do. I can ultimately say I love this profession. Starting out in Media has given me a new perspective. This is where I want to continue my career in advertising, marketing and digital strategy. I am a self-driven individual that knows how to stay on top of day-to-day tasks. My family has always told me I would make a good boss, because I would always keep everyone on task even at a young age. Through my experience at Love Advertising I have found that keeping on top of others is something that I am accustomed to and naturally take charge in order to make sure the job gets finished.

My skills in CS6 as well as advertising research, leadership, Strata and digital advertising has helped me adapt to the intense timelines and pressure inherent to the industry. My desired choice of career in advertising and marketing would be brand management. This position will allow me:

- Opportunity to shine at any marketing agency
- To use my research capabilities as well as other skills to achieve more awareness for the brand and help other members of the team become informed about the brand

I would greatly appreciate an opportunity to be apart of the VI Marketing and Branding family. I look forward to hearing from you.

Sincerely,

405.853.5375

ashley.m.quimby@gmail.com 14107 Blisswood Drive

Houston, TX 77044

Ashley Químby



14107 Blisswood Dr.

Houston, TX 77044

405-853-5375

ashley.m.quimby@gmail.com

Career Objectives

The ability to expand my knowledge in Planning, Strategy, and Search Engine Optimization (SEO) at an organization that will help me achieve my career goals and succeed to my satisfaction. Build upon my current skill set, which includes Strata, SBMS, SQUAD, and Print Buying.

Work Experience

Assistant Media Planner/Buyer Love Advertising, Houston, TX

February 2013-Present

- ∞ Print and Digital buys for CenterPoint Energy, Buffalo Wild Wings and Texas Renaissance Festival
- ∞ Evaluate and research all clients and promotions sent to the agency
- Assist Senior Media Planner/Buyers with weekly tracking of buys and research
- Finalize all monthly Media Billing for the agency

Account Service/Media Intern

August 2012-December 2012

Ackerman McQueen, Oklahoma City, OK

- Search Engine Marketing (SEM)- Proactive in the contributions of developing effective ad groups and keywords for the Chickasaw Nation's online search campaign. SEO copywriter for Chickasaw Nation Cultural Center online advertisements.
- Assisted with focus groups, market research and gathered insight for projects
- ∞ Gained viewers for the Chickasaw.tv network by contacting potential viewers across the nation
- Knowledgeable in media buying through the use of an online media system

Lindsey+Asp, University of Oklahoma

May 2012-December 2012

Project Manager/Account Lead

- Project Manager: responsible for final authorization for all projects leaving the agency
- Account Lead of Center for Children & Families, Inc. (CCFI) and worked to put together a virtual tour of the facility to gain prospective donors.

Marketing Intern January 2012

KJ Productions Marketing Group, Inc., Enid, OK

- Conducted market research to determine potential opportunities to attract new clients in the
- oilfield industry
- Assisted with advertising production at KJ Productions
 Served as associate producer for the shooting for Travis and Presley instruction videos

Shift Leader February 2010-December 2012

Jimmie Austin Golf Club, Norman, OK

- Created a new menu for the golf course grill Managed customer cash and credit transactions
- makes Responsible for customer orders at the Clubhouse grill and delivered beverages to customers on

Education

University of Oklahoma, Norman, OK Bachelor of Arts in Journalism Major: Advertising Combined GPA: 3.10 December 2012

Projects

Cameroon Tourism, University of Oklahoma

Spring 2012

- ∽ Developed an entire strategic plan to increase American tourism in Cameroon, Africa
- Chosen from a competitive competition to travel to Cameroon and pitch a campaign to the Minister of Tourism. The country is currently implementing the plan.

National Student Advertising Competition, University of Oklahoma

August 2011-December 2012

- Project manager for the 2012-2013 competition for Glidden Paint
- Leadership team member Worked with other members to put together an integrated marketing campaign for Nissan in 2011-2012 regional competition where we placed second.
- Implemented a variety of research techniques including a research experiment, focus groups, personal interviews, surveys and ethnographies.

Academic Experience

Advertising Club, American Advertising Federation, University of Oklahoma August 2011-December 2012